Mr…
The mafia
You can't kill the same mobster
fuck
If you break the rules
You know what happens, right?
If you kill me
you die too
If you get caught, you die, motherfucker.
IC
Where, where are you, hey!
Uh, hey!
Hey, open the door
Open the door, fuck
give up
Anyway, in 30 minutes
It's all over
What the fuck are you talking about?
Why, why not?
why! Ai!
We're on the same side
You shouldn't be like this
It's all over, why are you like this?
Please come to your senses!
Even if you saved Lee Yoon-seo and Kim Jun-hee,
After all, they are citizens
Because you are a mafia
We can't live together!
Oh, fuck, Oh Jeong-won
when a person dies
Hearing is the last thing
Being alive
You know?
listen carefully
Fuck you, Lee Yunseo.
you too die
Annahee?
Then check to see if it is dead after 30 minutes.
send message
Ah, it's cold
Uh, blanket, blanket.
fuck
Go Gyeongjun?
Ah, Mr.
Ah, it's cold
Fuck, why is this happening, why is this happening?
Why is it turning off?
Who is it?
Who is it!
don't do it
Don't do it, why are you doing this?
Don't do it, don't do it
Wow, Mr.
Oh, fuck, who are you?
Why! Why are you doing this to me?
Oh, fuck!
don't come
Don't come, you bastard!
Fuck, why! why!
Why do you even have to die!
If I didn't kill him
You were going to kill me!
ah! Get out! Ouch!
ah! Fuck! go away!
overnight
Eunchan Lim and Mina Choi
executed by the mafia
Eunchan Lim and Mina Choi’s occupations are
I am a citizen
From now on, all participants
find the mafia
Please start voting
If you're going to do this
kill me too
Why did you spare me?
Whatever you want anyway
To end
I have to die too
But why did you keep me alive?
Why did you keep me alive!
What the hell are you thinking, huh?
I can't talk for long now
For now
Jindabeom, solve it first
That's it
What does it all mean?
Did you kill the kids?
Answer me
Hey
Speak up!
Hey, calm down.
talk to you later
Hey, Oh Jeong-won
Hey!
Hey Junhee
What did he do to us?
When Jindabeom meets you
They'll try to kill you, be careful.
Jeongwon is
Why did we save it?
Okay, don't think about it anymore.
Anyway, now they both
I can't believe it
First of all, let’s vote for Zindabeom.
Let's think about what to do
What do you mean?
If we all vote for Zindabeom
I won't stay still
I'll do anything
And even if Jindabeom dies
Oh Jeong-won remains.
It's a disadvantage at night
We have to solve it before then
you
What are you thinking?
If not
I have to stop it even if it means killing me.
Because I don't know what will happen
I'll go to the warehouse.
Let's go together
no
I'm taking a break
Why? I want to go too
Listen to me, there are kids on the second floor!
I'll come back quickly
I'm locking the door
Yeah
♪ Happy birthday ♪
- What?
- fish
“Happy birthday”
fill me up
-Thank you
- Do you like it?
I like it so much
There is no garden?
But I
Why did you keep me alive?
Why did you keep me alive!
I can't talk for long now
This doesn't make sense
Jindabeom is gone
I'll look for you, so you're Yoon-seo...
That's it
I won't be fooled by you anymore
He really wants to kill us all.
- It's dangerous.
- Stop it!
Hey
You're a mafia too
Just for me and Yunseo
You and Jindabeom are the same
Yoonseo!
They are doing so damn well.
don't come
Don't do it, you crazy bastard.
Stop and leave Yoon Seo alone.
Go Kyung-jun and Shin Seung-bin
Did you kill him?
With those bastards
Do you like being the same guy?
Shut up, fucking bitch.
There's no need to do this
How is it to see you again?
Nice to meet you, right?
What you want to kill
It's me
Leave Yoon Seo alone.
I really want to do that too
But what should I do?
Fuck, I can't stab you.
- So what should we do?
- What?
I have to finish what I couldn't do yesterday
go up
- Fall?
- Yeah.
If I can't kill you, you have to die.
- 안 돼, 안 돼, 안 돼
- 넌 좀 닥치라고, 씨
씨발, 그만 좀 해
이 개새끼야
야, 차라리 나한테 해
씨발, 너도 빠져
닥치고 구경이나 해!
But
What happens next when I die?
Are you going to release Yoon-seo?
- No.
- That's
I saw you doing it
Even if I die
You won’t save Yun-seo.
Oh, so you don’t want to run?
- What, fuck, should I kill you now?
- That's not it!
I want to do it too
This is also against the rules
I don't think it will work?
What are you saying, Mr.
Mafia can't commit suicide
I can't die on my own
No, why can't I do it?
Then what is Choi Joo-won?
That was a violation of the rules, so he was executed.
My situation is different
Don't come, fuck it
Because you threatened me to death
you are killing me
Shut up and run quickly, Mr.!
Yesterday in the freezer
Don't you remember the warning?
you
Is it because you want to die together?
Don't come, fuck it
Just run! 씨
개새끼야!
개새끼
죽어, 이 개새끼야!
- are you okay?
- 어
놔, 이 개새끼야
으아, 씨발!
just
Let's die together
Yoonseo!
Yoon Seo-ya
Hey, you crazy bastard!
나 너무 아파
야, 이 개새끼야!
hey!
Oh, fuck
Jindabeom said
died
- Jin Bum’s occupation is
- Are you okay?
It's the mafia
Hold on
I need to come to my senses
-Are you hurt?
- Yoon Seo-ya
- I'm fine.
- Oh, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts
- What should I do?
don't say
- Oh, it's okay, it's okay.
- Don't say it.
I tried to solve it
Why did you do that! why!
I'm sorry
I think I know who you are now, you
I missed you
Se-eun
But
Stop it now
I'm sorry
me too
I couldn't help it either
I know
It's okay
So
Stop it now
Yoon Seo-ya
Yoonseo!
Come to your senses, Yoon Seo, come to your senses!
Yoon Seo-ya
Just hold on a little longer
I'll let you out.
No way
Garden,
Yoon Seo-ya
Hey, Lee Yunseo!
Hey, hey, Yoonseo!
Oh Jeong-won
died
Oh Jeong-won's occupation is mafia.
mafia game
Ends with a victory for the Citizens team
Hey Junhee
wake up
Kim Jun-hee!
Leave it alone!
If you touch it while connected to the server
You could fall into a coma
"Preparing"
"death"
"Done"
us
Do you remember?
These are Se-eun’s parents.
This…
What is it all about?
How was the game?
The feeling of dying
Was it scary and painful enough?
What?
Why are these kids like that?
What did you do?
don't worry
Everyone is just asleep
Although unconscious
the pain is real
This is all a game?
When did you come here?
It hasn't been long
Just the number of games
It's already been dozens of times
reality and
Because time in the game is different
But Jeongwon was originally
Win every game by yourself
It's set up
This is the first time you won
What did you do to Jeongwon?
Did I help you?
tell me
Because you need to know to fix it
I woke you up to ask you that.
alternative
Why are you doing this, why!
In the world my daughter created
You have to pay for your sins
What crime?
‘What crime’?
What crime did you say just now?
no fault
The crime of harassing our Se-eun
Rumors without substance
I believe it's real
The sin that sent you to hell!
That's a sin
Ic, hey, hey, fuck off
Why, what, what
What, what, what?
- What are you doing? give it
- Is this guy collecting porn again?
Oh, give it to me!
- Oh, give it to me.
- Oh, wait.
- What, hey, catch that guy.
- Oh, give me some.
- Take a quick look...
- That's so fucking funny.
Taste…
Oh, give me the phone!
Ah, Mr.
"This video
Play it live"
“Yes”
- Oh, I'm a celebrity, a celebrity.
- You're so sexy
Hey, celebrity, celebrity
Hey, hey, hey
Hey
Where are you going?
Hey, Se-eun
Park Se-eun!
Hey, what's wrong with him?
I don't know
My classmate died
But why
Why is no one taking responsibility?
Don't you?
I'm afraid that some harm will come to me.
‘It was a joke’, ‘It was a misunderstanding’, ‘I don’t know’
Just making excuses
no one's fault
I didn't admit it
no one
That's why I made this game
Our Se-eun felt
Pain!
To make you feel the same
what have you done
To teach you
yes
You are our Se-eun
I know you were a special friend
Then I should have saved him!
Why did you let me die?
No different from those kids
Because memories are erased every time
You'll never get used to the pain
It will be new every time
live forever in the game
Please…
Me too
Se-eun
I miss you so much
alone
How hard was it?
I'm sorry I didn't know
If someone has to take responsibility
I will do it
So the other kids
please send me home
Yes?
you
I'm out of my mind now
It hasn't come back completely.
If you overdo it, it can hurt
I am
I don't care if it hurts at all
So do it with me
Please send the kids...
Kids…
Please let the kids go, kids…
That kid found his memories
Jeongwon helped me
as a birthday present
So that I can get my memories back
I changed the settings
What do you want to say?
Suicide is
It wasn't an option.
Won-in really says she is Se-eun
I thought and acted
I made a choice to save my children.
Come to your senses!
That's not my daughter
Caused by settings
It's just an error
come out
That's
It's not just an error
The garden was the will!
If like Jeongwon
Our Se-eun also plays this game
What if you don't want to?
What if revenge is all about our greed?
no
It's still far away
Risking their lives
You saved your friend's life
Even if not all
To our Se-eun
Some kids felt guilty
If this is enough, we can do it once
I can give you a chance
Let’s send it all and watch.
no
i can't do that
Get out of the way, out of the way!
Our Se-eun
You're not dead now
Ah, sir, I lost again, sir, ah
Oh, what a surprise.
Ah, yes, Mr. Kim.
Where?
The bus stopped?
uh? W, hello? hello?
No way
Subtitle: Lee Hye-in